I'm doing a radio show.
Oh, hey, MBS!
They always tell me to stay away from the microphone.
That's it! That's what this is all about, right?
People have been gathering around me for a long time.
I almost never wash my pajamas.
What's your wash cycle?
A month or two.
One month, two months.
Well, here he is again today, the kettle man from the Starlust Sugar Refinery.
Today's guest is here!
This is my idol!
Hello everyone!
Is it this way, that way, or Harima?
I'm Kana Harima.
Nice to meet you.
Starlust's high school solo idol.
Thank you for coming to high school!
Mr. Harima has finally arrived!
Thank you very much.
She's been asking for this show for a while now, and I think she got it from the top.
I think it's from the top of the place, but you said you wanted to be in this show.
I've been watching this show for a long time.
I've been watching since Ai-chan started.
I wondered when I would be invited.
I wondered if this was Yakan-kun's order of favorites.
What are you talking about?
Mr. Harima.
Speaking of my love for Mr. Harima...
You know how much I like Mr. Harima, don't you?
Thank you very much.
For everything you've done for me...
It's my pleasure.
It's been a while, but...
Mr. Harima, I heard you've been very active recently.
I'd like to hear about that.
In the last year, you've appeared in nine plays?
That's right.
That's amazing.
I was surprised even by myself.
Nine isn't that amazing.
I've been pretty busy.
I've been pretty busy, and I've been doing interviews with Harima-san.
I knew I had a role to play.
I didn't want to lose it.
He said he didn't like it.
I never said that.
You said that.
I won't give you that big information impression.
I won't.
I said I wouldn't do that if I was playing a role.
I don't want to sound like I'm bragging.
But I'm surprisingly okay with it.
I see.
But that's an auto-off switch.
Some people are like that.
But I'm sure you have your own memories of each of the nine roles.
Well, in the beginning...
I played a lot of cheerful roles in the beginning.
Like, bright and young.
Younger than my age.
Like a high school student or a junior high school student.
I also have a lot of kindergarten-aged roles.
It's not that it's easier for me to play these roles.
I'd like to exaggerate myself a little bit.
I often play roles where I can exaggerate my brightness a little more to make myself look like that.
Since the summer, I've been playing roles where I'm cheerful on the outside, but I'm really thinking about things on the inside.
I've been playing roles where I'm cheerful on the outside, but I'm really thinking about things on the inside.
I started to play roles with a little more depth.
I started to play more and more roles in the summer.
That's when I started to take my acting more seriously.
The morning play in January of this year.
At first, I thought
It's a very cheerful role, but it's not
A very cheerful role, but with a bit of a grudge.
but I felt like he had something in his gut.
as the story unfolds.
That's right.
I was pretty much inspired by Takito-san.
Oh...
Is that okay? I'm sorry to hear that.
Not at all.
And Kyoko Koizumi from Odoru Daishousai.
Oh!
You were in the movie version.
I did it with that image in mind.
Based on that play.
I got a great reaction from the fans.
That made me happy.
I see.
So... in June...
The event, Tokyo Yayakan Land, will be held on June 6th, and I'm looking forward to seeing you there.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. But, you know, you're going to appear everywhere.
I've told you how I feel about the stage, and I'd like to ask you about it.
Is this an event with a play?
I wonder how much you can offer to the audience.
Don't raise the bar.
What?
I'm a little nervous.
Please tell me. If there's something you want to do...
This is the staff of Tokyo Yayakan Land, so...
Acting
If it's a play, what kind of role would you like to play?
If it's a play, I've never played a role like a heroine before.
What?
A heroine role.
Heroine.
I'd like to play a heroine.
Heroine sounds great.
I'd like to play a leading role.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You have Harima-san's score!
Let's use the points you got at the Staples Festival!
Thank you very much. Yay!
My three main elements
This program is
Mr. Aero-Kay
Mr. Soccer Kid
Mr. Cribbon
Toshikazu-chan
Time is Kinnari, I'm Masanari-san
Thank you very much!